suitcaseentrepreneur.com 2019-02-17

# Privacy Policy | Live a Location Independent Nomadic Lifestyle with Freedom | The Suitcase Entrepreneur

**BY VISITING THIS WEBSITE, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

 **OVERVIEW**  
I am committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information I collect through this web site at www.suitcaseentrepreneur.com (the “Site”), and how I collect and use that information.

The terms “I,” “me,” and “my” refers to Natalie Sission d/b/a The Suitcase Entrepreneur. The terms “user,” “you,” and “your” refer to site visitors, customers, and any other users of the site.

The term “personal information” is defined as information that you voluntarily provide to me that personally identifies you and/or your contact information, such as your name, phone number and email address.

Use of the Site, including all materials presented herein and all online services provided, is subject to the following Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all site visitors, customers, and all other users of the site. By using the Site or Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.

 **INFORMATION I COLLECT**

 **Contact Information:** If you provide me with your email address, you agree to receive emails from me. I require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * I may use the information to improve my products and services.
  * I may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, I may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. I may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

If you do not want to receive emails, you may opt out or change your preferences in your account settings. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates and offers.

You may choose to delete your personal information in the following way:

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at [va@suitcaseentrepreneur.com](mailto:va@suitcaseentrepreneur.com)

 **ACTIVITY**  
I may record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. I use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. I also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site.

 **COOKIES**  
I may send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of my service. The term “cookies” refers to small pieces  
of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. I may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.

 **THIRD PARTY LINKS**  
The Site may contain links to third party websites. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information I collect from you on my Site. Other sites accessible through this Site via links or otherwise have their own policies in regard to privacy. I am not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.

 **SECURITY**  
I maintain security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure. However, no exchange of data over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. While I make every effort to protect the personal information you share with me through my Site, you acknowledge that this information could be accessed or tampered with by a third party. You agree that I am not responsible for any intercepted information shared through my Site without my knowledge or permission. Additionally, you release me from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

 **CHILDREN**  
To access or use the Site, you must be 18 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from using the Site.

 **UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION**  
You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by contacting me via email at support[at]suitcaseentrepreneur[dot]com.

 **CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  
You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. I will notify you of any changes to this privacy policy by posting those changes on this page.

 **CONTACT**  
If you have questions about my privacy policy, please email me at support[at]suitcaseentrepreneur[dot]com.

Updated: May 24 2018
